Maxwell Bruce

+61 406 030 344 MaxwellWallaceBruce@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/maxwell-bruce-b0a0771b1/ github.com/MWBruce

About

I am an Honours Computer Science student graduating in November 2024 with two past internships and experience as the treasurer of the Competitive Programming Club. This resume encapsulates my key experiences and skills, yet for more comprehensive insights and details about my professional path, I invite you to visit my professional webpage designed and developed by me at https://mwbruce.github.io/#.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science (GPA: 6.9/7.0)

Graduating November 2024

The University of Adelaide

Awards

Adelaide Summer Research Scholarship

2023/2024

Experience

SAAB Australia Modelling and Analysis Engineer (Software/ML) 11/2023 - Present

- Developed and validated models to simulate and analyse defence systems including and not limited to Generative Adversarial Networks, Diffusion Models, Convolutional Neural Networks and LSTM.
- Utilised Python and C++ in developing solutions to various defense projects.

Australian Institute for Machine Learning

04/2023 - Present

Machine Learning Researcher (Intern)

- Developed various machine learning algorithms allowing me to develop a foundation of machine learning knowledge.
- Currently in the early stages of trying to develop a research paper relating to machine learning and its possible financial applications.

RJC Evans & Co Pty Ltd 04/2020 - 04/2023

Accountant

- Prepared Income Tax Returns, Financial Statements for clients
- Corresponded with various clientele and ensured their financial responsibilities were in order.
- Interpreted and advised on interpretation of client financial positioning.

Community Engagement

Competitive Programming Club

11/2023 - Present

Treasurer (Volunteer)

- Compete in various competitive programming competitions in teams of three.
- Manage the club's financial responsibilities including cashflows.

Project Everest Ventures11/2020 – 12/2020

Trekker (Volunteer)

- Volunteered for just over a month in visiting numerous villages in Fiji in an effort to ascertain and integrate genetically modified plants that would be better able to handle the harsh weather conditions.
- Worked in a team of 20 people in performing economic research in village plant sales to overcome a lack of digitalized data.

Projects

HTML/CSS - https://github.com/MWBruce/MWBruce.github.io (Or web link https://mwbruce.github.io/#).

My professional website outlining all up to date projects I am doing and relevant information about me -

https://github.com/MWBruce/MWBruce.github.io (Or web link https://mwbruce.github.io/#).

Python- https: // github.com/MWBruce/Machine Learning Stock Price Prediction

Neural Network (Machine Learning) Algorithm not using any ML libraries that predicts the stock price of a stock based on information provided in its more recent quarterly report

C++ - https://github.com/MWBruce/DataModel

Web scraper for share prices on the New York Stock Exchange, in which I plan to integrate into a machine learning model.

Skills

- C++
- Machine Learning
- Python
- Algorithms
- Teamwork

- Attention to Detail
- Problem Solving
- Communication
- Leadership